Life is uncertain, so be assured that
you will be
happily protected. Presenting ICICI
PRI iProtect Smart, a term plan
that
provides financial security till the age of 10.
Flexibility in choosing plan options is provided.
[Music]
In this plan, the
life insured
gets life cover in case of accidental death or accidental death.
[Music]
[Music] In
this plan, the insurance company
provides premium tax benefits.
ICICI PRI iProtect Smart offers
both life cover and
full card life cover. The
first one is
Mustafa who gets the entire amount and a must bet.
Women get the entire amount and a solid sum
which gets 10% every year.
After 10 years, Priya has
reduced her tax liability by 10%.
Feeling safe in her fast-paced life, Priya said,  ICICI
Pro iProtect Smartwatch 1 crore
rupees De 20 life cover Dena
18000 annually Very serious illness pond 30
years ek bachchi luck nivesh ki tha
49 saal di umer wich Renu ek sever bizna dia pata laga
[Music]
Proportionately deducted
8968 per year
[Music]
[Praise]